<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Corporate Jewelry and Custom Awards]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Corporate Jewelry and Custom Awards]]></description>
        <link>http://www.corporatemetalsolutions.com/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2016 20:36:58 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="http://www.corporatemetalsolutions.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[About Us]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>About Us</h1><p>We carry all metal types [Pewter, Brass, Titanium, alloy metals, Sterling Silver, 8KT Gold, 10KT Gold, 14KT Gold, as well Platinum]. We also offer a selection of genuine gemstones, diamonds, to synthetics. We are able to provide continuity to maximize our distributors’ satisfaction and experience. Our 30 plus years of manufacturing experience give you the leading edge for success is a result of our pride for customer satisfaction and loyalty. Backed behind our limited life-time warranty, you are in good hands. We offer everything from jewelry, jewelry accessories, to 3D modeling, and much more. Just ask as we are here to help!</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/04d7a52664f126e198645e94dde9f4b8024fa675.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.corporatemetalsolutions.com/about-us/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">012f6b3f-0b51-4a20-a802-83c4c8902318</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2016 17:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cufflinks & Accessory Backs]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Cufflinks & Accessory Backs</h1><p>Corporate Cufflinks are an excellent way of incorporating company image into an exquisite gift – a gift that will always be worn with pride while your customer/s business is indirectly being branded. They're ideal for marking special days, events and milestones. We work with our corporate distributors and their customers on designing cufflinks for companies across the globe, and no matter your client's budget or even quantity you will enjoy how CMS is very flexible to work with.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/cac76b0b7362d205414ac49de8a6ca8b6ff2416d.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.corporatemetalsolutions.com/corporate-cufflinks/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">8682a9ab-d504-47d2-97b2-fa5475c8e6ee</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2016 20:36:54 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Accessories]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Accessories</h1><p>Pendants and charms can come with a standard chain for presentation purposes; we has over 900 chains to choose from to ensure your client/s budget is properly utilized with our [Made in Italy] chains. </p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/7f65804512b24acee0f7f664faef980be1c3ecce.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>www.elinejewellers.com</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">1dddc1cb-c5b3-4f6a-9777-be670fdad02a</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2016 18:49:52 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Top Five Reasons Why Lapel Pins are Still Awesome!]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Top Five Reasons Why Lapel Pins are Still Awesome!</h1><p>2)  Recognition pins can help improve employee morale, and are a unique way to recognize the personal accomplishments of each individual on your staff. They can be used to celebrate workplace safety, employee attendance, sales achievements and just about any other noteworthy accomplishment.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/ea1bd9772a1c4f731a6f2d23534689697dd717e1.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>www.elinejewellers.com</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">ee465d28-e805-407d-a2dd-3fb7e23b6512</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2016 18:49:31 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Corporate Jewelry]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Corporate Jewelry</h1><p>In the era of strong competition, business companies do everything possible to maintain their customers. Apart from keeping customers and business clients satisfied, it is also very important to keep employees happy and motivated by giving some gifts to them for their good performance.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/67d38f3e66d32add786315ef1ab6c4e49bcd8dad.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.corporatemetalsolutions.com/corporate-jewelry/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">e728804f-5c7b-4377-ac91-54f82e9bb6f4</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2016 17:11:43 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Custom Made Coins]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Custom Made Coins</h1><p>Commemorative coins have a distinct design with reference to the occasion on which they were issued. Many coins of this category serve as collectors items only, while in corporate, schools, organizations they serve several purposes.   </p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/1fcc1ccd45686498b946e9f825e68954b866eae7.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.corporatemetalsolutions.com/commemorative-coins-have-a-distinct-design-with-reference-to/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">78252ba9-fe57-41ba-8f3b-8c6ff92124e3</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2016 17:10:39 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Services For Retail & Jewelers ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Services For Retail & Jewelers </h1><p>Custom jewelry is a self-reflection with intent to impress those around you.  We work with you and our designers to ensure your customer's jewelry piece is designed with attention to detail and care.  With flexible and unique variables, custom jewelry is a fun and an exclusive way to build your jewelry store collection.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/a7bd6ad640a50423f89953304f3cd4d45e478e73.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.corporatemetalsolutions.com/for-retail-stores/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">cfc2b8fa-3092-48b9-a2e8-649fc22be932</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2016 17:10:27 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[President Club Programs]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>President Club Programs</h1><p>Building a successful President’s Club program is crucial for “corporate leader identity” presented at a jubilee gala separating this award from all others as the most distinguished valuable award within corporate synergy.  Everything from design, to presentation are key essentials to a successful program.  The President’s Club Ring identifies leaders who have dedicated themselves to the beliefs and fundamentals as well the synergy the corporation has been founded on and lives by.  These people already have the homes, cars, as well travel they ever wanted but like all Dukes and Duchess; the jewel of the kingdom needs to be officially worn on one’s finger to truly feel part of the elitists.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>www.elinejewellers.com</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">0c431aa2-8e01-495a-8c57-dda188d0ae72</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2016 17:03:48 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>