<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Corporate Jewelry and Custom Awards]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Corporate Jewelry and Custom Awards]]></description>
        <link>http://www.corporatemetalsolutions.com/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2016 21:36:33 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="http://www.corporatemetalsolutions.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[About Us]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>About Us</h1><p>We carry all metal types [Pewter, Brass, Titanium, alloy metals, Sterling Silver, 8KT Gold, 10KT Gold, 14KT Gold, as well Platinum]. We also offer a selection of genuine gemstones, diamonds, to synthetics. We are able to provide continuity to maximize our distributors’ satisfaction and experience. Our 30 plus years of manufacturing experience give you the leading edge for success is a result of our pride for customer satisfaction and loyalty. Backed behind our limited life-time warranty, you are in good hands. We offer everything from jewelry, jewelry accessories, to 3D modeling, and much more. Just ask as we are here to help!</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/4a01a289144d369f7fa8a03a1a0d3c9fe7ed16b2.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.corporatemetalsolutions.com/about-us/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">012f6b3f-0b51-4a20-a802-83c4c8902318</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2016 18:58:17 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[President Club Programs]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>President Club Programs</h1><p>Building a successful President’s Club program is crucial for “corporate leader identity” presented at a jubilee gala separating this award from all others as the most distinguished valuable award within corporate synergy.  Everything from design, to presentation are key essentials to a successful program.  The President’s Club Ring identifies leaders who have dedicated themselves to the beliefs and fundamentals as well the synergy the corporation has been founded on and lives by.  These people already have the homes, cars, as well travel they ever wanted but like all Dukes and Duchess; the jewel of the kingdom needs to be officially worn on one’s finger to truly feel part of the elitists.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/af5a8fce2e183684bdd6fb1c00d55b6f9081eb15.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>www.elinejewellers.com</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">0c431aa2-8e01-495a-8c57-dda188d0ae72</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2016 17:48:14 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Accessories]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Accessories</h1><p>Pendants and charms can come with a standard chain for presentation purposes; we has over 900 chains to choose from to ensure your client/s budget is properly utilized with our [Made in Italy] chains. </p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/7381936672922aa2a086f274322e955d6d2ec2d7.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.corporatemetalsolutions.com/accessories/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">1dddc1cb-c5b3-4f6a-9777-be670fdad02a</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2016 21:36:09 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Top Five Reasons Why Lapel Pins are Still Awesome!]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Top Five Reasons Why Lapel Pins are Still Awesome!</h1><p>2)  Recognition pins can help improve employee morale, and are a unique way to recognize the personal accomplishments of each individual on your staff. They can be used to celebrate workplace safety, employee attendance, sales achievements and just about any other noteworthy accomplishment.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/ea1bd9772a1c4f731a6f2d23534689697dd717e1.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>www.elinejewellers.com</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">ee465d28-e805-407d-a2dd-3fb7e23b6512</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2016 12:37:31 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>